mididb.com 2002-06-03

# Ifni Music Privacy Policy

  **Site Map:**  

  **Partners:**  

| 

> **Ifni Music** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for our Web sites: Ifni MIDI, MIDI Database, Country MIDI, Angel Grrl Free Music, and Pop MIDI. 
> 
> ### Information Automatically Logged
> 
> We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. This allows us to detect broken links, mis-named files and similar site technical problems.
> 
> ### Advertisers
> 
> We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. We do not use cookies in other parts of our Web site, however, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company. We do not have access to this information.
> 
> ### Newsletter Registration Form
> 
> Our site's registration form REQUIRES users to give us contact information (their email address), and requests, but does not REQUIRE, demographic information (like name, age and city). 
> 
> Contact information from the Newsletter registration form is used only to distribute information about changes to our web site.
> 
> Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
> 
> Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, by adding content that we think they might like.
> 
> ### External Links
> 
> This site contains links to other sites. **Ifni Music** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
> 
> ### Security
> 
> This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Data is maintained on secured servers, accessible only to our administrative staff. Individual users are given a password that allows them to update or delete data previously submitted.
> 
> ### Children's Guidelines
> 
> We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children: 
> 
>   1. We will NOT collect or use personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent.
>   2. We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information at any time.
>   3. When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to: 
>     1. Respond directly to the child's request once and will not re-contact the child for any other purposes.
>     2. Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification.
>     3. Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a Newsletter subscription) and not re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity.
>   4. We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any receiving our Newsletter service.
>   5. We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child.
>   6. We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected.
>   7. We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online.
> 

> 
> ### Choice/Opt-Out
> 
> Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us.
> 
>   1. You can visit the following URL: [http://www.listbot.com](http://www.listbot.com/)
> 

> 
> ### Data Quality/Access
> 
> This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:
> 
>   1. You can visit the following URL: [http://www.listbot.com](http://www.listbot.com/)
> 

> 
> ### Contacting the Web Site
> 
> If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 
> 

### More great FREE MIDI at:

### [Free Music Directory](http://www.freemusicdir.com/cgi-bin/directory/in.cgi?id=mididb)

### [Top 52 MIDI](http://www.top52.com/cgi-bin/sites/rankem.cgi?id=mididb) | [MIDI Elite](http://www.midielite.com/cgi-bin/top/rankem.cgi?id=mididb) | [Top 219 MIDI](http://www.top219.org/vote.php?midi&140)

##### Copyright ©1996-2002 by [Ifni Music](http://www.ifni.com/)  
Last Update 1 June 2002

|  

  **Top Sites:**
